// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single

export const quiz = {
    totalQuestions: 15,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Which hockey team has won the most Stanley Cups?',
        choices: [
        'Montreal Canadiens', 
        'Toronto Maple Leafs', 
        'Detroit Red Wings'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Montreal Canadiens',
      },
      {
        question: 'Where was the coldest temperature recorded in the mainland US (-70F)?',
        choices: [
        'Oklahoma', 
        'Montana', 
        'New Hampshire'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Montana',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the name of the ice-skating rink in Central Park, NY?',
        choices: [
        'Wollman Rink', 
        'City Park Ice Rink', 
        'Rockefeller Ice Rink'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Wollman Rink',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which is the only country to have won a medal at every Olympic Winter Games?',
        choices: [
        'Germany',
        'United Kingdom',
        'United States'
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'United States',
      },
      {
        question: "Iconic 90s rapper Vanilla Ice's real name is:",
        choices: [
            'Marshall Mathers',
            'David Burd',
            'Robert Van Winkle'
            ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Robert Van Winkle',
      },
      {
        question: '"Winter is Coming" is the house motto of which family in Game of Thrones?',
        choices: [
        'House Stark',
        'House Targaryen',
        'House Greyjoy'
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'House Stark',
      },
      {
        question: 'Tracy Lauren Marrow starred on Law & Order SVU for 20 years. He is better known as:',
        choices: [
            'Ice-T',
            'Vanilla Ice',
            'Ice Cube'
            ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Ice-T',
      },
      {
        question: '"WHERE IS MY SUPER SUIT?!" is spoken by which ice-themed animated superhero in The Incredibles (2004)?',
        choices: [
            'Fro-zone',
            'Fro-yo',
            'Freezer Man'
            ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Fro-zone',
      },
      {
        question: 'What viral video "challenge" from 2014 helped raise $220 million dollars for ALS research?',
        choices: [
            'The Ice-Bucket Challenge',
            'The Ice-Tea Challenge',
            'The Ice Machine Challenge' 
            ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'The Ice-Bucket Challenge',
      },
      {
        question: 'This frozen beverage predates the Slurpee by 8 years:',
        choices: [
            'ICEE',
            'Slushie', 
            'Daiquiri' 
            ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'ICEE',
      },
      {
        question: 'In the 2nd episode of the hit TV show LOST (2004), what out-of-place animal is seen charging toward a group of characters on the jungle island?',
        choices: [
            'Polar Bear',
            'Caribou', 
            'Moose'
            ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Polar Bear',
      },
      {
        question: "Which Albertson's location has the coldest winter temperatures?",
        choices: [
            'North Dakota',
            'Montana',
            'Oregon'
            ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'North Dakota',
      },
      {
        question: 'The first frozen food items were sold commercially in what year?',
        choices: [
            '1937',
            '1930',
            '1922'
            ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '1930',
      },
      {
        question: "Albertson's very first store in 1939 sold homemade ice cream called:",
        choices: [
            "Uncle Al's Ice Cream Cones",
            "Idaho Classic Ice Cream Cones",
            "Big Joe's Ice Cream Cones"
            ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: "Big Joe's Ice Cream Cones",
      },
      {
        question: "Boise, ID (home of Albertson's) had its snowiest day on record in 1996, with how much snow?â€‹",
        choices: [
            '9.8 feet',
            '6.7 feet',
            '7.2 feet'
            ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '9.8 feet',
      },
    ],
  }